Thanks everyone!
It feels like my battle fatigue is melting away...
Your breasts aren't large enough to get tired.
Seems like everything is going fine today.
Julicia!
Scarlet!
So this is the hot-springs, huh?
It is bigger than I thought. I'm so surprised.
What a child.
Hot springs should be a place for relaxation.
This is so relaxing.
This is my first time.
Feels good.
My boobs are bigger.
Seems like it.
What is with that attitude?!
The captain said that they were beautiful.
What do you mean by that?
I want to know more about that.
I feel like my wounds are healing faster.
So this is hot spring huh?
We need to control these if I want to control Lemuria.
We have already started with our research.
We've collected plenty of samples.
If you put it on your skin it becomes so smooth that you might become younger.
Smooth, smooth, it's so nice, Nayuta-sama!
Smooth, silky.
I don't feel like getting out.
Listen, we must teach the students about more erotic stuff.
I need one more!
Do they know how much pressure I go through every day?
No they don't.
I need a snack!
Look here trainer!
I became so cute!
The energy isn't properly tuned yet.
There's an event happening.
Where?
Sengita.
I want to go.
They look dumb.
You're all here?
Lets go to the next stage.
Ok.
Understood.
Captain!